Toyoaki Uehara papers, 1945-1990 C611
Indiana University Archives
- Electronic media, circa 1990s and undated; 21; genreform: 3½" floppy disks (Box 9)
  - Ofudesaki No. 4 (1994), undated (Box 9)
  - Home Matter Makingtosh [sic], undated (Box 9)
  - WP51 Home Matter Original IBM, undated (Box 9)
  - No. 2 Ofudesaki Preface; Introduction, undated (Box 9)
  - No. 3 Ofudesaki with Notes, 1993 (Box 9)
  - Ofudesaki No. 4 copy, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Tenrikyo, undated (Box 9)
  - IBM MS-DOS Shinto Myth 6+7, undated (Box 9)
  - Shinto Myth Capt. 6, 7, undated (Box 9)
  - Fundamentals of Japanese Drill Text [Title Page, Table of Contents] Less 1-17, undated (Box 9)
  - Fundamentals of Japanese Drill Text Less 18-26, undated (Box 9)
  - Fundamentals of Japanese Drill 1-17 WordPerfect, undated (Box 9)
  - Fundamentals of Japanese Drill 18-26 WordPerfect, undated (Box 9)
  - Fundamentals of Japanese Drill 1-17 SoloWriter, undated (Box 9)
  - Fundamentals of Japanese Drill 18-26 SoloWriter, undated (Box 9)
  - Indiana University Matters, undated (Box 9)
  - Vitae, undated (Box 9)
  - Vitae WPS WS, undated (Box 9)
- Administrative Files, 1972-1981 (Box 10)
  This series includes Uehara's I.U. departmental files, committee files, papers related to Tenri University and Tenrikyo Mission Headquarters in America, correspondence, classroom syllabi and teaching materials, Japanese language teaching materials, and exchange programs. "Departmental" folders contain a wide variety of records including reports, program reviews, course creation and scheduling materials, course evaluations, meeting agendas and minutes, memos, conference materials and correspondence, newsletters, and various other papers.
  - Departmental, 1980-1981 (Box 10)
  - University Committee for East Asian Exchanges, 1979-1980 (Box 10)
  - Lecture Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 10)
  - Departmental, 1979-1980 (Box 10)
  - Indiana-Tenri Faculty Exchange Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
    - Tenri Faculty Exchange - Susan Arkush, 1978 (Box 10)
    - Tenri Faculty Exchange - George Ellison, 1978 (Box 10)
    - Tenri Faculty Exchange - John Hangin, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Departmental Curriculum Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Departmental (Box 10)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 10)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 10)
  - Departmental Lecture and Occasion Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 10)
  - East Asian Reorganization Committee EALL + EAST, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
  - East Asian Studies Program, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Departmental Curriculum (Undergraduate), 1974-1975 (Box 10)
  - EAST Grants Committee, 1973 (Box 10)
  - East Asian Studies Program, 1973 (Box 10)
  - East Asian Studies Policy Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - Departmental, 1972-1974 (Box 10)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 10)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - J511 Japanese Bibliography, 1968-1973 and undated (Box 11)
  - Comparative Religion (World Religion), undated (Box 11)
  - Syllabus E395, undated (Box 11)
  - M.A. and Ph.D. Programs, undated (Box 9)
  - Ph. D. Completed, undated (Box 9)
  - Morris Jacobsen Chap. III, undated (Box 9)
  - Promotion Committee for Iwamoto, undated (Box 9)
  - M.A. Completed, undated (Box 11)
    Photographs from this folder have been transferred to the IU Archives Photograph Collection. Contact the Archives Photograph Curator for more information.
  - East Asian Studies Center, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Departmental (Box 11)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 11)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 11)
  - East Asian Study Center, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Departmental, 1987-1988 (Box 11)
  - University Committee for East Asian Exchanges, 1986-1989 (Box 11)
  - Departmental (Box 11)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 11)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Yasuda Project (Box 11)
    - 1982-1987 (Box 11)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 11)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 11)
    - 1982-1983, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 11)
  - Indic Studies, 1981-1982 (Box 11)
  - University Committee for East Asian Exchanges, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
  - Departmental, 1971-1972 (Box 12)
  - Department of Religion, undated (Box 12)
  - East Asian Studies Program, 1970-1972 (Box 12)
  - CIC, 1971-1972 (Box 12)
  - Departmental, 1970-1971 (Box 12)
  - Far Eastern Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 12)
  - Committee on East Asian Studies, 1969-1970 (Box 12)
  - CIC, 1969-1970 (Box 12)
  - Departmental, 1969-1970 (Box 12)
  - CIC, 1968-1969 (Box 12)
  - Departmental, 1968-1969 (Box 12)
  - CIC, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Departmental, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - CIC, 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Departmental, 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - CIC, 1966 (Box 12)
  - Departmental, 1965-1966 (Box 12)
  - CIC, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Departmental, 1964-1965 (Box 12)
  - CIC, 1964 (Box 12)
  - Departmental, 1963-1964 (Box 12)
- Correspondence, 1951-1989 (Box 13)
  Correspondence mainly includes personal letters, cards, and postcards dated 1951-1989. Dr. Uehara traveled regularly in the United States and Japan, and exchanged frequent letters with his wife, son, and various family members. He also maintained regular correspondence with former students and attendees of Japanese language school programs. He also received communications from exchange fellows, colleagues and committee members, researchers, members of Shinto temples in Japan, Michigan, and Hawaii, and various friends from around the globe. Many of the letters in the collection are from professors and friends in Tenri, as well as with pastors and members of Tenrikyo Mission Headquarters in America in California, with some from those in other Tenrikyo branches. A significant portion of these materials are entirely in Japanese.
  Frequent correspondents include: wife Kiyoko Uehara, son Osamu Uehara, artist Shuko Kobayashi, President of Tenri University Kikuo Tanaka, Professor and E.A.L.C. Chairman Yu Ju Chih, Southern California School of Theology professor Floyd Ross, Asianist researcher Peter Metevelis, and former executive of The Boy Scouts of America Milton "Milt" Critchfield and his sons Chris and Ted Critchfield.
  - 1951-1964, (19 folders) (Box 13)
  - 1965-1973 and undated, (17 folders) (Box 14)
  - 1974-1982, (17 folders, 1 folder 1968-1977) (Box 15)
  - 1983-1989, (14 folders) (Box 16)